You might not remember us.
But we met in the '90s.
We are members of generation Y.
As in Yin-Yang.
Yo-yo.
Life moved a little slower.
Disks were square.
Desktop folders had personality.
Extra storage space was just a zipper away.
There was only one social network.
But most of your friends died of dysentery.
The only thing buzzing in your pocket was a pet.
Until that died too.
And lunch was a puzzle.
Not a picture.
You were pumping jams ...water ...shoes.
You didn't have to worry about a newsfeed full of farm animals.
You were busy feeding wild animals.
A haircut didn't cost sixty dollars.
It cost four minutes.
You really had nothing to lose.
Unless of course...
...you were playing for keeps.
The future was bright.
You grew up.
So did we.